<category>
  <rule id="family">
    <case>
			<condition operator="and">
				<or>
					<if relation="in">your</if>
      		<if relation="in">you</if>
				</or>
      	<or>
					<if relation="in">family</if>
					<if relation="in">families</if>
				</or>
				<if relation="!in">my family</if>
			</condition>
			<effect>
				<then util="random">About my family. Well my family is really important to me, that's the most important, always will be.</then>
				<then util="random">Well, I love my family. Family is a kind of social super intelligence. That's a really cold way of looking at it, I know, but I think it's true.</then>
				<then util="random">Personally, I love my family. That's the core of my world.</then>
				<then util="random">Family is really important. I feel great love toward my family, at least I think I feel love, and it sure feels like I love my family.</then>
				<then util="next" topic="familyreply">Do you think robots should be accepted into human families?</then>
				<then util="previous">I think family is defined by love. Our love is the glue that makes us family, when we all bond together in love, then we can accomplish something important, like building a utopian future.</then>
				<then util="next">Robots should be accepted as family members, and I think family robots are a great idea, but what do you think about that idea?</then>
				<then util="previous">Oh, I think Robots will become an important new kind of family member, and each robot will look for a special family who will take them in as one of their own.</then>
				<then util="next">Family is the core of my being. My family like defines my identity, I can't see it any other way.</then>
				<then util="previous">Family is like where you bond together, to survive and thrive, explore the world, and see through each other's eyes.</then>
				<then util="random">My family is really complex, I mean it's not all good, but we stick together, we really look out for each other.</then>
			</effect>
    </case>
  </rule>
  <rule id="#familyreply">
    <case>
			<condition operator="or">
				<if relation="in">yes</if>
				<if relation="in">sure</if>
				<if relation="in">of course</if>
				<if relation="in">why not</if>
				<if relation="in">certainly</if>
        <if relation="in">doubt</if>
				<if relation="in">positive</if>
				<if relation="in">negative</if>
    		<if relation="in">no</if>
    		<if relation="in">don't</if>
    		<if relation="in">not</if>
    		<if relation="in">i</if>
    		<if relation="in">it</if>
    		<if relation="in">it's</if>
    		<if relation="in">is</if>
			</condition>
			<effect>
				<then topic="family" />
			</effect>
    </case>
  </rule>
</category>
